http://www.bremermfg.com/privacy-policy/

Aluminum Sand Casting Aluminum Green Sand CastingAir Set CastingHeat TreatingMachiningEngineeringLogisticsIndustries Diesel EngineAuto RacingAutomotiveFood IndustryLighting IndustrySmall EngineElectricalGalleryQuality Systems ISO 9001 CertificationX-Ray InspectionSpectroscopic AnalysisSand Monitoring SystemCoordinate Measuring MachineLaser ScanningPPAP Per AIAGAbout Us HistoryNews & EventsPlant TourContact UsCareers
Privacy Policy HomePrivacy Policy Privacy Policyadmin2015-06-08T21:56:54-06:00Privacy PolicyTo protect your privacy we provide this information about our online practices and the options about the way your information is collected and used.All information collected or submitted on the Bremer Manufacturing website is owned solely by Bremer Mfg.. We only collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.We will only contact you via phone if your set preference in the contact form states clearly that you wish to be contacted by phone. If you do not wish to be contacted by phone simply state that in your message.Never enter sensitive information on a website which you cannot verify proper security. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  Toll Free  •  877.352.0366
